Associated Students of Duke University Records, 1965 - 1991 UA.31.02.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Committees, 1965-1991; 3
  - Athletic Council, 1972; 1982; 3_4
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Lacrosse, 1972 (Box 52)
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Swimming, 1972 (Box 52)
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Tennis, 1972 (Box 52)
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Track, 1972 (Box 52)
    - DUAC Questionnaires-Wrestling, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Recommendations on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1982 (Box 53)
- Legislature, 1967-1987; 4
  The Legislature Series include chronologically organized Resolutions and Statues passed between the ASDU Legislature between 1967-1987. The series also features files of the Speaker of Legislature, the records of the Legislative Ethics Committee, copies of the ASDU constitution and successive amendments, and the by-laws of the legislature. The Legislature series also includes administrative documents such as versions of the "Guide to Parliamentary Procedure" and instructions for drafting bills.
  - Resolutions, 1967-1973 (Box 53)
  - Resolutions, 1973-1979 (Box 53)
  - Shelved Legislation, 1960-1979 (Box 53)
  - Resolutions, 1980-1981 (Box 53)
  - RLIC-2-86-81, 1981 (Box 53)
  - Resolutions, 1984 (Box 53)
  - Tuition Resolutions, 1984 (Box 53)
  - Statutes-lists, 1967-1979 (Box 53)
  - Statutes, 1967-1973 (Box 53)
  - Statutes, 1973-1979 (Box 53)
  - Statutes, 1979-1981 (Box 53)
  - Statutes, 1984 (Box 53)
  - Budgetary Statutes, 1967-1975 (Box 53)
  - By-laws, 1968-1981 (Box 54)
  - By-laws, 1987-1988 (Box 54)
  - Constitution, Revision+Amendments, 1967-1979 (Box 54)
  - Guide to Parliamentary Procedure, 1972 (Box 54)
  - Parliamentary Procedure, 1976-1981 (Box 54)
  - Guide to Writing Bills (Box 54)
  - Legislative Ethics Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 54)
  - Legislative Responsibility Act, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Speaker's Files, 1984-1985 (Box 54)
  - Past Lobbying, 1980-1987 (Box 54)
  - Resolutions--list (incomplete), 1967-1979 (Box 54)
- Minutes, 1967-1989; 5
  The Minutes Series contains meeting minutes from sessions of the ASDU Legislature and Executive Council from 1967-1989. The records provide information about the issues discussed at these meetings, committee reports and the resolutions and decisions that occurred.
  - Legislature, 1967- Spring 1970 (Box 54)
  - Legislature, Spring 1971 (Box 54)
  - Legislature, 1971-1972 (Box 54)
  - Legislature, 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Legislature, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
  - Legislature, 1974-1975 (Box 55)
  - Legislature, 1975-1976 (Box 55)
  - Legislature, 1976-1977 (Box 55)
  - Legislature, 1977-1978 (Box 55)
  - Legislature, 1978-1979 (Box 55)
  - Legislature (includes committee notes and resolutions), 1980-Fall 1981; 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Legislature (includes committee notes and resolutions), 1980-1981 (Spring) (Box 55)
  - Legislature (includes committee notes and resolutions), 1981-1982 (Fall) (Box 56)
  - Legislature (includes committee notes and resolutions), 1981-1982 (Spring); 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Legislature (includes committee notes and resolutions), 1982-1983 (Fall) (Box 56)
  - Legislature (includes committee notes and resolutions), 1982- 1983 (Spring) (Box 56)
  - Legislature, 1984-1985 (Box 57)
  - Legislature, 1985-1986 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
  - Executive Committee/Legislature Meeting, March 15, 1982 (Box 57)
- Subject Files, 1972-1991; 6
  The Subject Files series contains memorandum, reports, clippings and other materials related to a number of ASDU initiatives. The series is arranged alphabetically. Topics include alcohol and drug policies, housing policies and dining services. Also included is information related the Social Impact of Duke Investments campaign against companies that supported apartheid in South Africa, including student letters asking the administration and Board of Trustees to end support.
  - 24 Hour Library, 1976 (Box 58)
  - Academic Council, 1980-1981 (Box 58)
  - ASDU Records, 1965-1983 (Box 58)
  - Adopt Your Campus, 1990 (Box 58)
  - Advising, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Advising Center Recommendations, 1977-1978 (Box 58)
  - Advising: J. Porter Durham Statement, 1981 (Box 58)
  - Advising, Pre-Professional Survey: Neil Shore, Kim Matthews, Lois Wood, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972 (Box 58)
  - Affirmative Action: Plan for Equal Opportunity, 1973 (Box 58)
  - Affirmative Action: Plan for Academic Personnel, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Alcohol Awareness, 1981 (Box 58)
  - Alumni Admissions/Alumni Scholarship, 1989-1990 (Box 58)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1981-1987 (Box 58)
  - Alumni Association 1989 (Box 58)
  - Alumni: Career Advising/Duke Network, 1981-1982 (Box 58)
  - Alumni: Duke Experience Survey, 1986-1987 (Box 58)
  - Alumni Relations, 1982 (Box 58)
  - Alumni: Students + Young Alumni, 1985-1988 (Box 58)
  - Alumni: University Development, 1980-1981 (Box 58)
  - Amendment I, 1986 (Box 58)
  - Appointee Requests, 1978-1980 (Box 58)
  - Army ROTC, 1980 (Box 58)
  - Arts, Duke University Support of the, 1977 (Box 58)
  - Arts and Sciences/ Trinity College Reorganization, 1990 (Box 59)
  - Athletics, 1972-1974 (Box 59)
  - Athletics, 1974-1975 (Box 59)
  - Athletics, 1976 (Box 59)
  - DUAC Questionnaire - Summary of Results 1972 (Box 59)
  - Athletics, 1976-1977 (Box 59)
  - Athletics: Retiring Chris Moreland's Number, 1988 (Box 59)
  - Auxiliary Services - General, 1990 (Box 59)
  - Baldwin Federation Report, 1974 (Box 59)
  - Beer-For-Points, 1982 (Box 59)
  - Beta Phi Zeta, 1982 (Box 59)
  - Black Affairs: General, 1981 (Box 59)
  - Black Affairs 1983-1987 (Box 59)
  - Black Affairs: Search Committee, 1978 (Box 59)
  - Black Affairs: Misc, 1981 (Box 59)
  - Black Affairs: Task Force, 1981 (Box 59)
  - Black Studies, 1975 (Box 59)
  - Black Studies: Task Force, 1975 (Box 59)
  - Black-White Relations (1 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 60)
  - Black-White Relations (2 of 2), 1982-1986 (Box 60)
  - Buckley Amendment (Privacy/Student Records), 1974-1975 (Box 60)
  - Bryan Center, 1986 (Box 60)
  - Bus Service to Chapel Hill, 1981 (Box 60)
  - Campus Drive Development Project, 1981 (Box 60)
  - Campus Enhancement, 1984-1985 (Box 60)
  - Capital Campaign, 1985 (Box 60)
  - Card Gym, 1980 (Box 60)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1978 (Box 60)
  - Central Campus, 1983 (Box 60)
  - Check Cashing, 1984-1985 (Box 60)
  - Classes: 8:00 AM, 1979 (Box 60)
  - Computer, 1985 (Box 60)
  - Cooperative Program, 1979 (Box 60)
  - Conference on Career Choices, 1980-1983 (Box 60)
  - Counseling and Psychological Services (CAPS), 1986 (Box 60)
  - Coffeehouse, undated (Box 61)
  - Dean of Arts and Science Luncheons, 1990 (Box 61)
  - Dean of Student Life Search, 1981 (Box 61)
  - Developmental/Annual Fund, 1979-1981 (Box 61)
  - Distributional Requirements, 1978 (Box 61)
  - Duke/Durham Day, 1984 (Box 61)
  - Duke Drama (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 61)
  - Duke Drama (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 61)
  - Duke Drama Cable 13 Report, 1988 (Box 61)
  - Duke University Food Service (DUFS), 1977-1978 (Box 61)
  - DUFS - Problems, 1980-1981 (Box 61)
  - DUFS, 1982-1983 (Box 61)
  - DUFS, 1985-1986 (Box 61)
  - DUFS: Privatization, 1985 (Box 61)
  - DUFS: Action Items, 1985 (Box 61)
  - DUFS, 1986-1990 (Box 62)
  - DUFS: Misc, 1986-1990 (Box 62)
  - Duke Stores, 1986 (Box 62)
  - Duke University Volunteer Service, 1986 (Box 62)
  - Duke University Medical Center, 1987 (Box 62)
  - Durham, 1981-1982 (Box 62)
  - Durham Human Relations Commission, 1981 (Box 62)
  - East-West Expressway Reactions, 1972-1975 (Box 62)
  - East-West Expressway Environmental Statement, 1972 (Box 62)
  - East Campus: Architecture Selection Committees, 1984-1985 (Box 62)
  - East Campus Center, 1975-1980 (Box 62)
  - East Campus Enhancement, 1984-1986 (Box 62)
  - Ecos v. Volpe, 1982 (Box 62)
  - Emory Activity Fee Task Force Survey, 1981 (Box 62)
  - Energy, Voluntary Conservation, 1977-1980 (Box 62)
  - Engineering, 1981 (Box 62)
  - Enrollment, 1990 (Box 62)
  - Fall Break, 1981 (Box 63)
  - Federations, 1971-1982 (Box 63)
  - Faculty Relations, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Financial Aid, 1973-1974 (Box 63)
  - Financial Aid, 1974-1976 (Box 63)
  - Financial Aid, 1978 (Box 63)
  - Financial Aid, 1981-1982 (Box 63)
  - Final Four, 1988-1990 (Box 63)
  - Free University, 1976 (Box 63)
  - Freshman Clusters, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1975-1981 (Box 63)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1984-1986 (Box 63)
  - Freshman Orientation, Jan 1984 (Box 63)
  - Graduate and Professional Student Council, 1972-1990 (Box 63)
  - Gyn Survey, 1977-1978 (Box 63)
  - H. Keith Brodie, 1985-1990 (Box 63)
  - Honor Code, 1978-1981; 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Honor System, 1978 (Box 64)
  - Hospital Unionization, 1979 (Box 64)
  - Housing, 1971-1979 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Dorm Proposals, 1970-1988 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Evaluation, 1974 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Federations, 1980 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Implementation, 1981 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Judicial System, 1970-1978 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Locator Service, 1977-1979 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Problems, 1979-1980 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Policies, 1979-1981 (Box 64)
  - Housing: Residential Questionnaires, 1980-1981 (Box 65)
  - Housing: Student Response to RLTF, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Housing: Transfer Students, 1977-1981 (Box 65)
  - House Courses, 1980-1982 (Box 65)
  - Hotel Development, 1981 (Box 65)
  - ICC Report: Educational Policy, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Improving Undergraduate Instruction: The Student's Role, undated (Box 65)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1981-1985 (Box 65)
  - Interaction Coordinator, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Klan and Nazi Activities, 1981 (Box 65)
  - Kolena Case, 1981 (Box 65)
  - Labor Union Activities, 1977-1978 (Box 65)
  - Legal Affairs, 1975-1979 (Box 65)
  - Lightning on Campus, 1981 (Box 65)
  - Long Range Planning, 1980-1990 (Box 65)
  - Major's Union, undated (Box 65)
  - Mail System, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Management Sciences Class Project/Report: "Duke University", 1976 (Box 65)
  - Management Sciences, 1977-1979 (Box 65)
  - Maintenance, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1976 (Box 65)
  - MLK Day, 1986-1989 (Box 65)
  - Minority and Female Faculty, 1988-1990 (Box 65)
  - Nature Conservancy, undated (Box 65)
  - Networking, 1985-1986 (Box 65)
  - Nixon Library, 1981 (Box 66)
  - Nixon Library, 1981-1982; 3 Folders (Box 66)
  - North Carolina Student Rural Health Coalition, 1978-1979 (Box 66)
  - Office for Experimental Learning, 1978 (Box 66)
  - Parking Proposal, 1977 (Box 66)
  - Placement Office, 1982-1987 (Box 66)
  - Pre-College Program, 1978 (Box 66)
  - Physical Plant Maintenance, 1981 (Box 66)
  - Programs of Study, 1973-1978 (Box 66)
  - Privacy Policy, 1977 (Box 66)
  - Program in Science, Society and Human Values, 1978 (Box 66)
  - Programs, Interdisciplinary Courses, 1976-1979 (Box 66)
  - Proposed English I Requirement, 1976 (Box 67)
  - Provost Agreements, 1968 (Box 67)
  - Public Policy Studies, 1975 (Box 67)
  - Public Policy Majors Union, 1981 (Box 67)
  - Public Safety, 1975-1982 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board, 1974-1979 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board, 1976-1982 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board, 1978-1991 (Box 67)
  - Rally, 1979 (Box 67)
  - Reagan Visit, 1988 (Box 67)
  - Recreation and Sports Clubs, 1976 (Box 67)
  - Retrenchment, 1977-1980 (Box 67)
  - Retrenchment: ASDU Response, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Retrenchment: Correspondence and Misc, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Retrenchment: Faculty Response, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Retrenchment: Nursing School, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Retrenchment: Physical Education Department, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Retrenchment: Residential Life Proposals, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Retrenchment: Sociology Department, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Retrenchment: Student Response, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Retrenchment: Summaries of Proposals, 1980 (Box 68)
  - Student Rights, 1976 (Box 68)
  - Senior Citizens, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Sex, 1983 (Box 68)
  - Sexual Assault and Harrassment, 1981-1982 (Box 68)
  - SPUD (Student Project for Universtiy Development), 1977-1978 (Box 68)
  - Social Implications of Duke Investments, South African Divestment (1 of 4), 1985-1986 (Box 68)
  - Social Implications of Duke Investments, South African Divestment (2-4 of 4), 1985-1986; 3 folders (Box 69)
  - Policy Implementation Committee Records, 1986 (Box 69)
  - South Africa Letters, 1985; 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Student Activities, 1986 (Box 69)
  - Student Affairs: General, 1982 (Box 69)
  - Student Concern Center, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Student Discipline: Drinking and Noise Problems, 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - Student-Employee Relations, 1980-1986 (Box 70)
  - Student-Faculty Relations, 1979-1984 (Box 70)
  - Student Health, 1980-1984 (Box 70)
  - Student Health Advisory Questionnaire, 1976-1977 (Box 70)
  - Student Health: Infirmary, 1984 (Box 70)
  - Student Life, 1984-1986 (Box 70)
  - Student Loan Fund, 1976 (Box 70)
  - Student Services, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Student Surveys (Box 70)
  - Summer Storage, 1980 (Box 71)
  - Symposium, 1982 (Box 71)
  - Teacher-Course Evaluation Form, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Teaching Grants (undergraduates), 1978-1979 (Box 71)
  - Tenure, 1975-1977 (Box 71)
  - Terry Sanford, 1969-1970 (Box 71)
  - Title IX, 1974 (Box 71)
  - Title IX Dispute, 1980 (Box 71)
  - Transportation, 1977-1986 (Box 71)
  - Trnity Council, 1980-1981 (Box 71)
  - Tuition, 1984-1985 (Box 71)
  - Tuition Survey, 1984 (Box 71)
  - Undergraduate Enrollment, 1978-1980 (Box 71)
  - University Center, 1981-1982 (Box 71)
  - Vans, 1979-1980 (Box 71)
  - Video Tape and Cable, 1976 (Box 71)
  - Visitor's Center, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Volunteer Center, 1988-1990 (Box 71)
  - The Weisfeld Case, 1981 (Box 72)
  - Women's Studies, 1980 (Box 72)
  - Women's Symposium, 1978 (Box 72)
  - X-rated film policy, 1977 (Box 72)
  - Young (Student) Trustee, 1977 (Box 72)
  - Young Trustee Program, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Misc, 1981 (Box 72)
- General Materials, 1955-1990; 7
  The General Materials series contains additional information about the structure and initiatives of ASDU. The Administrative Materials subseries contains internal planning and evaluation documents and other materials collected and used by ASDU officers. The Publications and Reports subseries includes materials published and used by ASDU such as committee reports, copies of the Student Directory and the ASDU Update newsletter.
  - Administrative Materials, 1955-1990; 1
    The Administrative Materials subseries includes information about ASDU elections and referendums, the history of ASDU and materials related to membership in regional and national student organizations. The subseries also contains copies of the ASDU constitution, information about the 1979 re-organization and other miscellaneous documents.
    - Administrative Information, 1988 (Box 72)
    - ASDU Stationary (Box 72)
    - ASDU Reorganization, 1979 (Box 72)
    - Elections, 1976-1990 (Box 72)
    - Elections and Referendum Results, 1973; 1981; undated (Box 72)
    - Elections: Fliers, 1968-1975 (Box 72)
    - Academic Vice-President Vacancy, 1989 (Box 72)
    - Personnel File, 1989 (Box 72)
    - Evaluations, 1984 (Box 72)
    - Evaluations, 1985 (Box 72)
    - Evaluations, 1986 (Box 72)
    - Evaluations, 1987 (Box 72)
    - Historical, 1984 (Box 72)
    - ASDU at a Glance, 1981 (Box 72)
    - Important Documents, circa 1974; undated (Box 73)
    - Student Gov Handbook, 1955-1956 (Box 73)
    - History of ASDU, 1977 (Box 73)
    - General Administrative Papers, 1977-1982 (Box 73)
    - 1st Constitution, 1969 (Box 73)
    - Guide to Parliamentary Procedure, 1972 (Box 73)
    - Conferences:AAUS, 1983-1990 (Box 73)
    - Conferences: ASA, 1981-1982 (Box 73)
    - Conferences: COPUS, 1980-1985 (Box 73)
    - NC-FICUS, 1983-1986 (Box 73)
    - National Student Organizations, 1980-1986 (Box 74)
    - ASDU Reunion, 1987 (Box 74)
    - ASDU Retreats, 1976-1979 (Box 74)
    - Meetings with University Officials, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Intercollegiate Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
    - Statements of University Officials, 1967-1974 (Box 74)
    - United Methodist Church, 1990 (Box 74)
    - DUU Programming Handbook, 1981-1982 (Box 74)
    - MISC Administrative Materials, 1985 (Box 75)
  - Publications and Reports, 1955-1990; 2
    The Publications and Reports subseries compiles materials ASDU published and distributed or used as references for decision making. These materials include copies of committee and task force reports from both ASDU and University committees, student handbooks and directories, ASDU newsletters. This subseries also contains clippings from The Chronicle discussing ASDU and other miscellaneous materials.
    - Academic Booklet, 1983 (Box 75)
    - An Analysis of the Proposed Picketing and Protest Policy, 1968 (Box 75)
    - Report of the Task Force on Black-White Relations, 1982 (Box 75)
    - Duke Dimensions, January 1981 (Box 75)
    - Duke Directory, 1984-1988 (Box 75)
    - Directions for Progress, 1980 (Box 75)
    - The Student Body's Response to Directions for Progress, 1980 (Box 75)
    - The Fifth Decade, 1964 (Box 75)
    - Financial Report, 1984 (Box 75)
    - The Glickman Report, 1974 (Box 75)
    - Final Report of the Task Force on Institutional Advancement and Alumni Affairs, 1981 (Box 75)
    - The Intellectual/Culture Climate at Duke, 1988 (Box 75)
    - Report of the Planning and Funding Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 75)
    - Planning for the Eighties, 1978 (Box 75)
    - Proposed Judicial Structure of Duke University, 1968 (Box 75)
    - Report of the Committee for the Study of Student Residential Life, 1969 (Box 76)
    - Final Report of the Residential Life Task Force, 1980 (Box 76)
    - Report on Year-Round Operations, 1980-1990 (Box 76)
    - Report on Undergraduate Concerns in Trinity College, 1988 (Box 76)
    - Report on the Institute for Undergraduate Curricular Reform, 1974 (Box 76)
    - Report of the School of Forestry, 1 of 3, 1984 (Box 76)
    - Report of the School of Forestry, 2 of 3, 1984 (Box 76)
    - Report of the School of Forestry, 3 of 3, 1984 (Box 76)
    - Structure and Choice in Liberal Eduction, 1986 (Box 76)
    - Student Perspective, 1970 (Box 76)
    - Student Project for University Development, 1976 (Box 76)
    - Summary Report of the University Planning Committee, 1972 (Box 77)
    - Urban Land Institute Study, 1976 (Box 77)
    - Published Material, 1966-1970 (Box 77)
    - Newsletters, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
    - Studies, Report, 1980-1981 (Box 77)
    - Memos, Circulors, 1980-1981 (Box 77)
    - ASDU Update, 1980-1981 (Box 77)
    - Executive Letter, 1981 (Box 77)
    - ASDU Communicator, 1982 (Box 77)
    - Newsletters, 1980 (Box 77)
    - ASDU Updates, 1982 (Box 77)
    - The Duke Bluebook, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 77)
    - Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 77)
    - MISC Clippings, 1980s (Box 77)
    - Memoranda, Reports, Misc, 1979-1983 (Box 78)
    - Correspondence,flyers, notices, etc (Box 78)
    - MISC, 1970-1975 (Box 78)
- Executive, 1972-1990; 8
  The Executive series contains materials gathered by executive officers of ASDU who serving in the years 1972 to 1990. Materials include correspondence, reports, memorandum, minutes and committee information. The Presidential Files subseries contains materials from the presidents of ASDU and the Executive Files subseries contains records produced by other executive positions. The Executive Council subseries contains the records of the main executive committee.
  - Presidential Files, 1972-1990; 3
    The Presidential Files subseries contains the correspondence, reports, notes and memorandum from ASDU presidents. The subseries is arranged chronologically by presidential administration with the bulk of the records dating from the early 1980s. Many of the files contain communications with Duke administrators including Terry Sanford, H. Kenneth Pye and William Griffiths. Also included are presidential speeches and addresses and a set of papers entitled "To the Next ASDU President" in which presidents gave advice on the responsibilities of the position to their successor.
    - Steve Schewel, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
    - Curt Martin (incoming correspondence), 1973-1974 (Box 1)
    - Curt Martin (outgoing correspondence), 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - Jeff Talmage (incoming correspondence), 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - Jeff Talmage (outgoing correspondence), 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - Rick Glaser (incoming correspondence), 1975-1976 (Box 1)
    - Rick Glaser (outgoing correspondence), 1975-1976 (Box 1)
    - Reggie Howard, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Kyle Citrynell, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
    - Gary Burchill, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
    - Frank Emory, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    - [Frank Emory Misc], 1979 (Box 2)
    - [Frank Emory: Personal Notes], 1979 (Box 2)
    - Christopher Hest, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Bryan Fair, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Bryan Fair Matter, 1980 (Box 2)
    - J. Porter Durham: Speeches, Notes (Box 2)
    - J. Porter Durham: Correspondence (Box 2)
    - From Porter Durham to Shep Moyle, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    - Shep Moyle: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Shep Moyle, 1 of 5, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Shep Moyle, 2 of 5, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Shep Moyle, 3 of 5, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Shep Moyle, 4 of 5, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Shep Moyle, 5 of 5, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Shep Moyle: Personal (Box 3)
    - Shep Moyle: Lector, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Shep Moyle: Files, 1978-1982; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Shep Moyle: Miscellaneous, 1978-1982; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - John Baker: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
    - Martin November, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
    - Martin November: Police Reports, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Randall Rainer, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Connie Pearcy: Summer Coresspondence, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Speeches and Addresses, 1984-1990 (Box 5)
    - Past Addresses of ASDU presidents to the Board of Trustees, 1986 (Box 5)
    - "To the Next ASDU President', 1972-1975 (Box 5)
  - Executive Files, 1972-1990; 4
    The Executive Files subseries contains correspondence, reports, notes and memorandum gathered by the executive officers of ASDU including the Vice-President at Large, Student Organizations Chairman, and Executive Secretary. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by position title. The papers contain information about the responsibilities of each executive position, current initiatives and working relationships between executives.
    - Administration: list of correspondents included, 1971-1974; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Administration: William Griffith, 1971-1974 (Box 5)
    - Executives, 1972-1975; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Executives, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
    - Executives, 1978-1979 (Box 78)
    - Adminsitrative Secretary, 1973-1979 (Box 78)
    - Attorney General, 1973-1978 (Box 78)
    - Buisness Manager, 1972-1977 (Box 78)
    - Executive Secretary, 1974-1977 (Box 78)
    - Speaker of the Legislature, 1977-1978 (Box 78)
    - Student Organizations Chair: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 78)
    - S.O.C: Correspondence, David Pyle, 1987 (Box 79)
    - S.O.C: Correspondence, David Pyle, 1988 (Box 79)
    - S.O.C: Correspondence, David Pyle, 1988 (Box 79)
    - S.O.C: Correspondence, David Pyle, 1988-1989 (Box 79)
    - S.O.C: MISC Correspondence, David Pyle, 1989 (Box 79)
    - Treasurer, 1971-1972 (Box 79)
    - Vice President, 1973-1977 (Box 79)
    - Vice-President, Engineering, 1975 (Box 79)
    - Vice-President, Engineering, 1981-1990 (Box 79)
    - Vice-President, Nursing School, 1981 (Box 79)
    - Vice-President, Trinity College, 1981 (Box 79)